

Ajona.09

@Ajona09

Compared to the compared to

German native

English fluent - C1

Spanish beginner

Soft Skills

technically savvy

creativity

adaptability

cooperation

organizing

scientific work

♂ Interests

Traveling

Cooking

Politics

Hydroponics

Movies

Science

Lists

Art

Certificates

Drivers License

B (car)

I'm a German student, passionate about filmmaking and sometimes traveling the world by bus & train. I have a solid background in intercultural studies, sociology, technical skills, applied creativity, and extensive experience in academic research.

I value art, science, sustainability, and social justice, and I aim to weave these principles into the projects I develop throughout my career.

Education

Technical Secondary School specializing in economics

Berufliches Schulzentrum Christoph Lüders Görlitz 2015 – 2017 | Görlitz, Germany

Physics (B.Sc.)

Brandenburg University of Technology Cottbus-Senftenberg 2017 – 2018 | Cottbus, Germany

Culture and Technology (B.A.)

Brandenburg University of Technology Cottbus-Senftenberg 2018 – 2024 | Cottbus, Germany

School of Arts and Design

University of Tsukuba 2023 – 2024 | Tsukuba, Japan semester abroad

Professional Experience

Student Council of Culture and Technology

Financier

2019 - 2023 | Cottbus, Germany

finance managing, helping students, planing and working at events

pool production GmbH - Filmfestival Cottbus

Intern at PR & Marketing 2021 | Cottbus, Germany

Volunteering at Goldeimer gGmbH

Support at Festivals 2023 – 2024 | Germany

Raspberry Pi, Audorino

DaVinci Resolve edeting, color grading, animation Audacity Inkscape HTML CSS Office Programms Word / Excel / PowerPoint Linux Single Board Computers